[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- [exhales]
[inhales sharply]
[急促吸气]
[all groan]
[众人呻吟]
- Come on, Ricky, you're taking forever.
快点，Ricky，你慢得像蜗牛。
- Mini-golf is a game of concentration and patience.
迷你高尔夫是讲究专注和耐心的游戏。
- Well, concentrate on this patience.
那就专注在这份耐心上吧。
Boom! I'm on a roll, 'cause my ball's in the hole.
砰！我状态正佳，因为我的球进洞了。
- That was MY ball.
那是我的球。
- Too late. I'm already dancing.
太迟了，我已经开始跳舞了。
- I feel like trying something new.
我觉得想尝试点新东西。
Let's go to this hole.
我们去这个洞吧。
- Ooh. Make a wish, then spin around real fast.
哦，许个愿，然后快速转个圈。
- Sold!
成交！
Ooh, I get to go again. That's what I wished for.
哦，我可以再玩一次。那正是我许的愿。
- There's no wishing in mini-golf.
迷你高尔夫里没有许愿这回事。
And you played these holes out of order.
而且你打这些洞的顺序不对。
- You need to lighten up, buddy.
你需要放松点，伙计。
So what club should I use here, guys?
那我在这里该用什么球杆呢，各位？
- You know, I would go with the putter.
你知道，我会选择推杆。
- You only have a putter.
- 你只有一根推杆。
It's always going to be a putter.
总是用推杆。
- Not if you use... a footer.
- 如果你用...脚踢的话就不一定了。
Dawn, Dicky, and Nicky: Goal!
黎明，迪基，尼基：进球！
- This is useless.
- 这毫无用处。
You three aren't taking this seriously.
你们三个根本没认真对待。
Even this course is a joke.
就连这个球场也是个笑话。
Spaceships, astronauts,
太空船，宇航员，
the fact that we're indoors.
我们居然在室内。
We should be outdoors with wooden windmills
我们应该在外面，有木制风车
and real wind.
还有真正的风。
- That is ridiculous.
那太荒谬了。
The stuff Dad put in here is awesome.
爸爸放在这里的东西很棒。
Oh. Except for that alien with the googly eyes.
哦，除了那个眼睛会转的外星人。
Seriously.
说真的。
Googly eyes freak me out.
眼睛会转的东西让我害怕。
- Since when?
从什么时候开始的？
- Aww, honey, Dawn seems a little sad.
哦，亲爱的，Dawn看起来有点难过。
Here, come cheer her up with one of your funny faces.
来，用你搞笑的表情逗她开心。
I'm going to get you.
我要抓到你。
[baby crying] I'm going to get you!
[宝宝哭泣] 我要抓住你！
- I don't know. It's just always been that way.
- 我不知道。一直以来都是这样。
All I know is those googly eyes
我只知道那些大眼睛
are just throwing me off my game.
让我完全失去了状态。
- Well, you know what's throwing me off my game?
- 那你知不知道是什么让我失去了状态？
Everything about this place.
这个地方的一切。
I'm surprised there's no techno music.
我惊讶这里居然没有电子音乐。
- That reminds me. Three, two, one, dance off!
- 这倒提醒了我。三，二，一，跳舞比赛！
[techno music playing]
[电子音乐播放]
♪ ♪
- There's no dancing in golf.
- 高尔夫球场里不跳舞。
- [sighs] I'm sorry, Ricky, but you're the only kid
- [叹气] 对不起，Ricky，但你是唯一一个
on the planet who would walk in here
走进这里
and not say this place is awesome.
却不觉得这个地方很棒的孩子。
- I would say this place is awesome,
- 我会说这个地方很棒，
buuuut it's not.
但事实并非如此。
- It's The But-er and those snobby country club kids.
- 都是因为那个“但是”，还有那些自命不凡的乡村俱乐部孩子。
- Dawn. - Madison.
- Dawn。 - Madison。
- Ricky. - Spaulding.
- Ricky。 - Spaulding。
- Nicky. - Lacey.
- Nicky。 - Lacey。
- Dicky. - Other guy.
Dicky. - 另一个家伙。
- Hamilton.
Hamilton。
- Really? All right.
真的吗？好吧。
Hamilton.
Hamilton。
- What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
- We heard your Dad opened up a new course,
我们听说你爸爸开了一个新球场，
and we wanted to check it out.
我们想来看看。
- Spaceships, lasers, aliens?
太空船，激光，外星人？
It's like Cirque Du So-Lame in here.
这里就像个无聊的马戏团。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Mini-golf should be played outdoors
- 迷你高尔夫应该在户外玩
with wooden windmills and real wind.
有木制风车和真正的风。
- I couldn't agree with you more.
- 我完全同意你的观点。
Now get out.
现在出去。
- Fine. Dawn.
- 好吧。Dawn。
- Madison.
- Madison。
- Ricky. - Spaulding.
- Ricky。 - Spaulding。
- Nicky. - Lacey.
- Nicky。 - Lacey。
- Dicky.
- Dicky。
- Guy whose name I still can't remember.
- 那个我仍然记不住名字的家伙。
- Hamilton.
- 汉密尔顿。
- Hamilton. Why won't that stick?
- 汉密尔顿。为什么就是记不住？
Hamilton, Hamilton, Hamilton.
汉密尔顿，汉密尔顿，汉密尔顿。
Hamilton.
汉密尔顿。
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ 嘿！ ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一、二、三、四！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na na ♪
♪ 一、二 ♪ ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一、二、三、四！ ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Ugh, what are you still doing here?
呃，你还在这里做什么？
- We were going to leave, buuuut...
我们本来要走的，但是...这个地方真的很适合评判人。
this place is really great for people judging.
哦。你不是说观察人吗？
- Oh. Don't you mean people watching?
哦，你不是说看人吗？
- No.
不。
Nice hat.
帽子不错。
[laughter]
笑声
- Wow. It's hard to believe that one of us
哇，真难以置信我们中有人
has something in common with them.
和他们有共同点。
- Yeah, Ricky, when she told us
是啊，瑞奇，当她告诉我们
how much she hated our golf course,
她有多讨厌我们的高尔夫球场时，
we thought for sure you were going to side with them.
我们以为你肯定会站在他们那边。
- [scoffs] Please.
哼，拜托。
- Got your usual smoothies.
拿到了你常喝的思慕雪。
Strawberry, strawberry, strawberry,
草莓味，草莓味，草莓味，
green tea with kale and a double brain boost.
绿茶加羽衣甘蓝和双倍脑力提升。
- What can I say, Dad?
我还能说什么呢，爸爸？
Most people zig. I like to zag.
大多数人走直线，我喜欢走曲线。
- Hey, those kids over there zag too.
嘿，那边那些孩子也走曲线。
They ordered the same thing. [laughter]
他们点了同样的东西。
So what'd you think of Get Golfy?
那你觉得Get Golfy怎么样？
- Well, the three of us loved it,
嗯，我们三个都很喜欢，
but Ricky thought it was a little...
但Ricky觉得它有点...
What'd you call it, Ricky?
你说它是什么，Ricky？
- An intergalactic disgrace.
一个星际耻辱。
- Hey, that's what the zaggers called it.
嘿，那就是那些追随者们叫它的。
- Hey, look. My straw looks like a mustache.
嘿，看。我的吸管看起来像胡子。
[gasps] Mustache straw fight.
[惊呼] 胡子吸管大战。
[cup clatters]
[杯子碰撞声]
- Oh, great! Do you know how hard it is
哦，太好了！你知道从羊驼那里获得双重脑力提升有多难吗？
to get a double brain boost out of alpaca?
[叹气]
[exhales]
我是说，能让我离开一下吗？
I mean, will you excuse me?
嘿，Ricky，你知道从羊驼那里获得脑力提升的是什么吗？
- Hey, Ricky, you know what gets brain boost
嘿，Ricky，你知道什么能从羊驼那里获得脑力提升吗？
out of alpaca, right?
什么？
- What? - Spaulding's father.
Spaulding的父亲。
He owns a chain of dry cleaners.
他拥有一连串的干洗店。
They're very good.
他们非常出色。
- Here's a coupon for 10% more.
这里有一张10%折扣的优惠券。
- Why would people pay 10% more?
为什么人们愿意多付10%？
- People love coupons.
人们喜欢优惠券。
- We've been watching you, Ricky.
我们一直在观察你，Ricky。
You really know your way around a mini-golf course.
你对迷你高尔夫球场真的很熟悉。
How would you like to know your way
你想不想熟悉一下
around the mini-golf course?
迷你高尔夫球场？
- You mean-- - Yes.
- 你是说—— - 是的。
The Boulderly Hills Country Club Mini-Golf Course.
博尔德山丘乡村俱乐部迷你高尔夫球场。
- Oh, I know the BHCCMGC.
- 哦，我知道BHCCMGC。
Is it true you have grass flown in from Japan?
听说你们从日本运来了草坪，是真的吗？
- Oh, yes, and Michigan.
- 哦，是的，还有密歇根。
- We think you're BHCCMGC material.
- 我们认为你是BHCCMGC的料。
So why don't you join us?
那为什么不加入我们呢？
Uh, I don't think I should.
呃，我觉得我不应该。
I'm already part of a foursome.
我已经是四人组的一员了。
- Olé!
奥莱！
[crash]
[撞击声]
- [sighs] It's complicated.
唉，这很复杂。
- Is it?
是吗？
You're better than them, Ricky.
你比他们强，里基。
Take the brochure. It's a scratch and sniff.
拿上这本小册子，它是刮刮闻的。
- And I'll take that coupon too.
我还要拿那张优惠券。
- Of course you will.
当然你会拿的。
- [sniffs]
[嗅]
Ah, Squishy, smell that glorious Michigan grass.
啊，Squishy，闻闻这美妙的密歇根草香。
That is not a cedar drawbridge.
那不是雪松吊桥。
[sniffs]
（嗅）
It is a cedar drawbridge!
那就是雪松吊桥！
- Hey, Ricky? - Nothing.
嘿，Ricky？
I was just reading an interesting article
没什么。
about new wind farm technology--
我刚才在读一篇关于新型风电场技术的文章——
- Oh, speaking of wind farm technology,
哦，说到风电场技术，
pull my finger.
拉一下我的手指。
[laughter]
（笑声）
- Please don't.
请不要。
- Speaking of don't, I did have a dream last night
说到不要，我昨晚确实做了一个梦
where I was chased by something called The Waffle-Nator.
梦里我被一个叫“华夫终结者”的东西追赶。
[as Schwarzenegger] Your syrup, give it to me, now!
[模仿施瓦辛格] 你的糖浆，给我，现在！
- Stop that. That's mine.
别那样。那是我的。
- Fine. But I'll be back.
好吧。但我还会回来的。
- Oh, waffles. Nice.
哦，华夫饼。不错。
- That's mine too.
那也是我的。
- Nom-nom-nom-nom-nom...
咔嚓咔嚓咔嚓咔嚓...
- Why do you have to chew like that?
你为什么非得那样嚼呢？
- It means I'm enjoying my food.
这意味着我正在享受我的食物。
Nom-nom-nom-nom...
- Sounds good. I want one.
听起来不错。我想要一个。
Oh.
哦。
both: Nom-nom-nom...
Nom-nom-nom...
- Ooh. That means I'm enjoying my food.
哦。这意味着我正在享受我的食物。
- Well, now I'm not enjoying my food.
好吧，现在我不享受我的食物了。
- Well, then you should be chewing like this.
那么，你应该这样咀嚼。
[both chewing loudly]
[两人大声咀嚼]
- I want in on this. Hold on.
我也想加入。等一下。
all: Nyach-nyach-nyach-nyach-nyach...
大家：Nyach-nyach-nyach-nyach-nyach...
- What is wrong with you people?
- 你们这些人怎么回事？
- Sometimes I have too good of a hair day,
- 有时候我头发状态太好了，
but besides that, I'm pretty happy with myself.
但除此之外，我对自己还是挺满意的。
- You three have no manners,
- 你们三个一点礼貌都没有，
no sense of the proper way to act,
不知道该怎么得体地行事，
and you wouldn't know Michigan grass from your elbow.
连密歇根的草和你自己的手肘都分不清。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- 哇，哇，哇！
Let's not bring Michigan into this.
咱们别把密歇根扯进来。
- Wow, Ricky, I didn't realize you were the expert on manners
- 哇，里奇，我没想到你对礼仪和行为举止这么有研究。
and the proper way to act.
以及行为的正确方式。
- I may not be an expert,
我可能不是专家，
but I was invited to play at the BHCCMGC yesterday.
但我昨天被邀请去参加BHCCMGC。
- The what?
什么？
- The Big Hairy Cow Chocolate Milk Gulping Contest.
大毛牛巧克力奶咕噜大赛。
Keep up, people.
跟上节奏，各位。
- No.
不。
I was invited to the Boulderly Hills Country Club,
我被邀请去了博尔德山乡村俱乐部，
and you weren't.
而你没有。
You know why?
你知道为什么吗？
Because I take things seriously,
因为我认真对待事情，
and you nyach-nyach-nyach-nyach-nyach.
而你只会嘻嘻哈哈。
- Oh, like you never nyach-nyach-nyach-nyach'd.
- 哦，好像你从来没有嘻嘻哈哈过。
- Yeah, I used to nyach-nyach and nom-nom,
- 是的，我曾经也嘻嘻哈哈和吃吃喝喝，
and even on occasion, I'd... [blows raspberry]
甚至偶尔，我还会... [吹口哨]
But you know what? I grew up.
但你知道吗？我长大了。
And you should too.
你也应该如此。
Now, if you'll excuse me,
现在，如果你们不介意，
I'm going to go play a round of proper mini-golf
我要去在城里最 exclusive 的俱乐部打一场正式的迷你高尔夫。
at the most exclusive club in the city.
祝你们有个好日子。
Good day.
早上好。
I forgot my brochure.
我忘了拿我的宣传册。
Good day!
早上好！
I promised Mom I'd walk him before I left.
我答应过妈妈离开前会遛他。
Final good day!
最后的早上好！
- Wow, can you believe the nerve of that guy?
哇，你能相信那家伙的厚脸皮吗？
He really thinks he's better than us.
他真的以为他比我们强。
- Well, he's not. - Yeah.
嗯，他不是。
- Yeah. We'll show him.
是的。我们会让他看到的。
- Not now, though, right?
不过不是现在，对吧？
- No, we're going to finish eating breakfast.
不，我们要吃完早餐。
[all chewing loudly]
[所有人都在大声咀嚼]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Ground control, it's Major Tom.
地面控制，我是汤姆少校。
- Yes, Tom?
是的，汤姆？
- Say it right. - [sighs and chuckles]
说得对。
Yes, Major Tom?
是的，汤姆少校？
- We got a squeaky rocket on hole number seven.
我们在七号洞有一枚吱吱响的火箭。
I'm going to give it a little bacon grease.
我要给它涂一点培根油脂。
- Please tell me "bacon grease" is just an expression.
请告诉我“培根油脂”只是一个表达方式。
- Yes, it is, Anne.
是的，安妮。
An expression of my genius.
我天才的表达方式。
It fixes squeaks and tastes great.
它既能修好吱吱声，又美味。
Mmm, liquid pig.
嗯，液态猪油。
[chuckles]
（轻笑）
Ground control,
地面控制，
we have a missing rocket.
我们有一枚火箭失踪了。
And a missing alien arm.
还有一只外星手臂失踪了。
Oh...
哦...
my...
我的...
gosh!
天哪！
No!
不！
- Tom, are you okay?
- 汤姆，你还好吗？
[sighs] Major Tom, are you okay?
[叹气] 汤姆少校，你还好吗？
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- 是的，我没事。
There's just a lot of missing stuff up here.
这里只是有很多东西不见了。
And I have a pretty good idea who's to blame.
而且我有个很好的想法，谁该为此负责。
Alien ghosts.
外星鬼魂。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
[upbeat whistling]
[欢快口哨]
- This is amazing.
这真是太神奇了。
You're chewing, and yet
你在咀嚼，可是
there are no "nom-noms" or "nyach-nyachs."
却没有'咔嚓咔嚓'或'喵喵'的声音。
How do you do it?
你是怎么做到的？
- We'll tell you our secrets
我们会告诉你我们的秘密
if you tell us how you scored a 39 today.
如果你告诉我们今天你是怎么得39分的。
That's only one off the course record.
那只比球场纪录少一分。
- I really believe the game is won
我真的相信比赛在你踏上球场之前就已经决定了胜负。
before you even step onto the course.
哦。
all: Ooh.
那很好。
- That's good.
- Let's not talk sport at lunch.
午餐时我们别谈体育了。
- Oh. Did anyone read that article
哦，有人读过那篇关于新风力发电技术的文章吗？
on new wind farm technology?
是的。
- Yes.
是的，我读过了。
Yes, I did.
瑞奇认为我们不适合这里。
- Ricky thinks we're not going to fit in around here.
是啊，我们和这些人一样有品位、有教养。
- Yeah, we're just as classy and sophisticated
哦。
as these people.
老兄，来一盒你最好的苹果汁，
- [British accent] Oh.
再加一根最弯的吸管。
My good man, a box of your finest apple juice
我的好先生，来一盒你们最好的苹果汁
with your bendiest straw.
配上你们最柔软的吸管。
- [British accent] And make it snappy.
- [英式口音] 快点儿。
We're classy, and we don't like to wait.
我们很高雅，不喜欢等待。
- Ooh. - Ooh, appetizers.
- 哦。 - 哦，开胃菜。
Don't mind if I do.
那我就不客气了。
[all chewing loudly]
[所有人大声咀嚼]
This place is so fancy, the food is pre-chewed.
这个地方太高级了，食物都是预先嚼过的。
- So, after reading that article,
- 所以，读完那篇文章后，
I have to say, it seems like a "wind-wind" situation.
我不得不说，这似乎是个“双赢”的局面。
[all laugh]
[大家笑]
[all chewing loudly]
[大家大声咀嚼]
Would you excuse me for just one moment?
能请你们稍等我一下吗？
I'm going to go hit the little putter's room.
我要去一下洗手间。
What are you guys doing here?
你们在这里做什么？
- Proving you're not better than us.
- 证明你并不比我们强。
- Well, you're doing a terrible job.
- 嗯，你们做得太差劲了。
You're dressed like idiots, and you're eating garbage.
你们穿得像傻瓜，吃的东西也像垃圾。
- [scoffs] - Wow, you are snobby.
- [嗤之以鼻] - 哇，你真势利。
- No, that's actually garbage.
- 不，那真的是垃圾。
[all chewing disgustedly]
[所有人都厌恶地咀嚼着]
Would you guys leave? You don't belong here.
你们能不能离开？你们不属于这里。
- But you do?
- 但你们属于这里吗？
- Yes, he does. He's a Vestie now.
- 是的，他属于。他现在是Vestie了。
That's what we call ourselves.
那是我们对自己的称呼。
- Richard came up with it.
- Richard想出来的。
- Because we all wear vests. - And we're besties.
- 因为我们所有人都穿背心。 - 而且我们是最好的朋友。
- So he belongs, buuuut you don't.
- 所以他属于，但是你们不属于。
So buh-bye.
所以再见。
- Well, then maybe we'll become members.
- 那么，也许我们会成为会员。
[laughter]
笑声
- You guys will never become members here.
- 你们永远不可能成为这里的会员。
- Really? Give us two reasons why not.
- 真的吗？给我们两个理由。
- Because you're classless garbage eaters
- 因为你们是无阶级吃垃圾的
and are terrible at mini-golf. - What are you saying?
而且迷你高尔夫打得糟糕。 - 你在说什么？
- I'm saying you're classless garbage eaters
- 我说你们是无阶级吃垃圾的
and are terrible at mini-golf.
而且迷你高尔夫打得糟糕。
- Say what you want about our classless garbage eating,
- 关于我们无阶级吃垃圾的事，你想怎么说都行，
but don't insult our mini-golf skills.
但别侮辱我们的迷你高尔夫技能。
- What mini-golf skills?
- 你们的迷你高尔夫技能是什么？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Care to make this interesting?
- 想让这变得有趣点吗？
- Well, first we'd have to replace you
- 嗯，首先我们得把你
with three interesting people.
换成三个有趣的人。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- We're talking about mini-golf.
- 我们在说迷你高尔夫。
Quads versus Vesties. Winner takes all.
四轮车对背心族。赢家通吃。
- All of what?
- 通吃什么？
- Your vests.
- 你们的背心。
[all gasp]
[众人惊呼]
- Well, you have nothing we want,
- 好吧，你们没有什么我们想要的东西，
so what would we win?
那我们能赢什么？
- [sighs] You can take everything you don't like
- [叹气] 你们可以把不喜欢的东西
out of Dad's golf course.
从爸爸的高尔夫球场里全部拿走。
[both gasp]
[两人同时惊呼]
- Deal. - Deal.
- 成交。 - 成交。
- Deal. - Hamilton.
- 成交。 - 汉密尔顿。
- You got it. - Yes!
- 你说的。 - 太好了！
Deal.
成交。
[rock music]
摇滚音乐
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- 哦，哦，哦，哦
- We are terrible at mini-golf.
我们在迷你高尔夫球上真糟糕。
How are we going to beat the Vesties without Ricky?
没有瑞奇，我们怎么打败Vesties呢？
- Yeah, Dawn. What were you thinking when you made that bet?
是啊，道恩。你下注的时候在想什么？
- I'll tell you exactly what I was thinking
我会告诉你我在下注那一刻的确切想法。
at the precise moment I made that bet.
我当时在想，“哦，我的天哪，我刚吃了垃圾。”
I was thinking, "Oh, my gosh, I just ate garbage."
哦。你好。
- Oh. Hello.
大家：你好。
all: Hello.
所以，冰淇淋，嗯？
- So ice cream, huh?
- 所以，冰淇淋，嗯？
[all chewing loudly]
[所有人都在大声咀嚼]
Do you guys ever take anything seriously?
你们这些人有没有认真对待过什么事情？
- I take The Waffle-Nator seriously.
- 我对《华夫终结者》可是认真的。
[as Schwarzenegger] I told you I'd be back.
[模仿施瓦辛格] 我告诉过你会回来的。
- You know, this is why I left you for the Vesties.
- 你知道吗，这就是我离开你们加入背心帮的原因。
And this is why you're going to lose the mini-golf challenge.
这也是为什么你们会在迷你高尔夫挑战赛中输掉。
- [sighs] Richard is so annoying.
- [叹气] 理查德真是烦人。
- Pardon me, I forgot I came in here for an apple.
- 抱歉，我忘了我是进来拿苹果的。
- Yeah, but he's right.
- 是啊，但他说的没错。
We don't take things seriously.
我们不认真对待事情。
That's why he's the only one out of us
这就是为什么他是我们中唯一一个
with any mini-golf skills.
有迷你高尔夫技能的人。
- Pardon me, I also forgot a napkin.
- 对不起，我也忘了拿一张餐巾纸。
- And the only one of us with any manners.
- 而且是我们中唯一一个有礼貌的人。
- Oh. And I forgot to say good day!
- 哦。我忘了说再见！
- But he's terrible at leaving a room.
- 但他在离开房间方面很糟糕。
- Oh, definitely. - The worst.
- 哦，绝对是。 - 最糟糕的。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Anne. - Hey.
- 安妮。 - 嘿。
- I just came from upstairs,
and there's a few more items missing.
- Huh, that's strange.
- Yeah. Strange is one word for it.
Here. Plug this in for me? - Sure.
- Another word for it might be,
you know, guilty! - Oh.
Tom, what are you talking about?
- You never liked that golf course, did you, Anne?
If that is your real name.
- You know it's Chantal, and I don't like it,
你知道我是Chantal，我不喜欢这个名字，
so I go by my middle name, Anne.
所以我用我的中间名，Anne。
What is your point?
你到底想说什么？
- What'd you do with my rocket?
你把我火箭弄哪儿去了？
- I don't know where your rocket is
我不知道你的火箭在哪儿
or any of your other stuff.
也不知道你的其他东西。
- Really? It's pretty hot under that light,
真的吗？那灯底下挺热的，
isn't it, Chantal?
不是吗，Chantal？
- Not anymore.
现在不了。
- Fine, I believe you...Anne.
好吧，我相信你...Anne。
[clears throat]
[清嗓子]
Here. Plug this in for me?
这里。帮我插上这个好吗？
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Dawn. - Madison.
- 道恩。 - 麦迪逊。
- Nicky. - Lacey.
- 尼基。 - 蕾西。
- Dicky. - Ricky.
- 迪基。 - 瑞奇。
- Dawn. - Ricky.
- 道恩。 - 瑞奇。
- Nicky. - Ricky.
- 尼基。 - 瑞奇。
- Okay, this is ridiculous. We know each other's names.
- 好吧，这太荒谬了。我们都知道对方的名字。
- So how's this going to work?
- 那么这要怎么进行呢？
- Our best three against you three.
- 我们这边最好的三个人对你们三个。
- Right. Hamilton, Lacey, you're out.
- 对。Hamilton, Lacey, 你们下场。
- All right. Let's do this thing.
- 好的。开始吧。
Quaddle up!
准备好了！
Um, sorry, Richard. Your team's over there.
呃，抱歉，Richard。你的队伍在那边。
- Oh, right.
- 哦，对。
- [coughs]
- [咳嗽]
[adventure music]
[冒险音乐]
♪ ♪
[romantic music]
[浪漫音乐]
♪ ♪
- Aw. You missed.
哎呀，你没打中。
[romantic music]
浪漫音乐
♪ ♪
- [coughs]
（咳嗽声）
- A little late.
有点晚了。
- No, I got one of Dicky's hairs in my mouth.
不，我嘴里进了迪基的一根头发。
- Did you just kick your ball closer to the hole?
你是不是把球踢得更靠近洞了？
That's cheating.
那是作弊。
- It's only cheating if someone sees it.
只有被人看见了才算作弊。
- I saw it.
- 我看到了。
- Did you?
- 是吗？
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
- I'm getting close, Anne.
- 我快接近了，安妮。
- Yeah. You're two blocks from Crazy Town.
- 是啊。你离疯狂镇只差两个街区了。
You have yourself as a suspect.
你自己也是嫌疑人之一。
- I'm not ruling anybody out.
- 我不会排除任何人。
- Forget it, Tom, it's miniature golf.
- 算了吧，汤姆，这只是迷你高尔夫。
- Oh, you're right. - I am?
- 哦，你说得对。 - 真的吗？
- Great idea. - What idea?
好主意。
- In order to find the culprit, I need a disguise.
什么主意？
- Um, I didn't say that.
为了找到罪魁祸首，我需要一个伪装。
Hi.
嗯，我没那么说。
[sniffing] Bacon?
嗨。
Bacon grease.
闻起来像培根？
The dog.
培根油。
Tom. - You mean Major Tom?
那只狗。
- He'll figure it out.
汤姆。
[upbeat music]
他会弄清楚的。
- How is the score so close?
比分怎么这么接近？
- If Dawn sinks the next putt, they win.
如果Dawn推进下一个推杆，他们就赢了。
- I got this.
我搞定这个。
Good luck, Dawn.
祝你好运，Dawn。
Try not to look at the alien,
尽量不要看那个外星人，
even though it's looking at you.
尽管它正看着你。
[all laugh]
大家都笑了
- Yeah, Dawn, try not to look at the alien.
是的，Dawn，尽量不要看那个外星人。
I mean, look at that thing.
我是说，看看那东西。
That dude is goo-guh-ly.
那家伙真怪异。
Eyes, eyes, eyes.
眼睛，眼睛，眼睛。
- Dicky!
- 迪基！
- Sorry. Putt away.
- 抱歉。放回去。
[ominous music]
[不祥的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Ah!
- 啊！
♪ ♪
[all groan]
[所有人都呻吟]
all: Yes! - We won!
所有人: 是的！ - 我们赢了！
Vesties: Vesties rule! Vesties rule!
背心队：背心队最棒！背心队最棒！
Vesties rule! Vesties rule!
背心队最棒！背心队最棒！
Vesties rule!
背心队最棒！
- Good game. You won fair and square.
- 好比赛。你们赢得光明正大。
- Yes, we did.
- 是的，我们确实赢了。
Isn't that right, Richard?
不是吗，理查德？
- No. It's not.
- 不，不是的。
We cheated.
我们作弊了。
- What?
- 什么？
- Madison kicked her ball.
- 麦迪逊踢了她的球。
- I did not! - You did too.
- 我没有！ - 你也有。
And now you're lying about it.
你现在还在撒谎。
You don't respect the game.
你不尊重比赛。
You don't care about honor or wooden bridges
你不在乎荣誉、木桥或密歇根的草地。
or Michigan grass.
你只在乎赢。
All you care about is winning.
我想要加入一个以正确方式比赛的团队。
I wanted to be on a team that played the right way.
而我选错了团队。
And I chose the wrong team.
他们可能是吃垃圾的人，
They may be garbage eaters,
但他们是优雅的吃垃圾者。
but they're garbage eaters with class.
谢谢，兄弟。
- Thanks, bro.
- 谢了，兄弟。
- Very, very moving, Richard.
- 非常非常感人，理查德。
Buuuut unless Dawn's ball magically falls into the hole
但是，除非Dawn的球神奇地掉进洞里
without her taking another stroke,
而她不用再打一杆，
we won, and they lost.
我们赢了，他们输了。
- Squishy, it was you?
- Squishy，是你吗？
I knew this disguise would work. Bring that back.
我就知道这伪装会奏效。把它拿回来。
I'm going to get you. I'm going to get you.
我会抓到你的。我会抓到你的。
- [screaming] Googly eyes!
- [尖叫] 弹珠眼！
- The ball went in. The Quads win!
- 球进去了。四分卫队赢了！
[all cheering]
[所有人欢呼]
- No fair. She bumped into me, and I hit it with my foot.
- 这不公平。她撞了我，我用脚踢到了球。
- That still counts. - That's cheating.
- 那也算数。 - 那是作弊。
- It's only cheating if someone sees it.
- 只有被人看到才算作弊。
- You saw it.
- 你看到了。
- Did I?
- 我看到了吗？
- You're no longer welcome at the club.
- 你不再受欢迎来俱乐部了。
- And you're no longer welcome here.
- 你也不再受欢迎在这里了。
As I said before, get out.
就像我之前说的，出去。
- I wanted that alien and that spaceship.
- 我想要那个外星人和那艘飞船。
- You'll get nothing and like it.
你什么也得不到，而且你得喜欢这样。
- Well, you're not getting our vests.
好吧，你别想得到我们的背心。
- Good, we didn't really want them anyway.
好啊，我们本来也不太想要它们。
They look stupid.
它们看起来很蠢。
Oh, it looks good on you, though.
不过，穿在你身上挺好看的。
- Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
- Our quaddles weren't the same without you.
没有你，我们的四重奏就不一样了。
- Now what?
现在怎么办？
- Now we dance.
现在我们跳舞。
Three, two, one!
三，二，一！
[techno music]
[电子音乐]
Tom: Squishy.
汤姆：软软。
Squishy. Hey, kids. Squishy!
软软。嘿，孩子们。软软！
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling]
[口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶耶耶，耶耶 ♪
♪ 耶耶，耶耶耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪